Kraushaar Galleries
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Correspondence, 1945-1968, Series 3:; (boxes 26-53; 27.75 ft.)
  - Me-Mu, General, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 29)
    (Montclair Art Museum; Museum of Art of Ogonquit)
  - Meta Mold Aluminum Company, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 30)
    (Frank Gelein, curator of the company's Art for Everyone exhibition)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - Munson-Williams-Proctor Institute, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - Museum of Fine Arts of Houston, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - Museum of Modern Art, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 34)
    (records of transactions with the Art Lending Service)
  - N, General, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 35)
    (Elizabeth S. Navas; Woldemar Neufeld)
  - Newman, Hélèe S., 1954 (Box 38, Folder 36)
  - O, General, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 37)
    (Verne Offerman)
  - Pa-Ph, General, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 38)
    (Philadelphia Museum of Art)
  - Pi-Pu, General, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 39)
    (Dorothy Poulos)
  - Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 40)
  - Philadelphia Art Alliance, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 41)
  - Q, General, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 42)
  - R, General, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 43)
    (Sidney Raynes; Billy Rose)
  - Sa-Si, General, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 44)
    (Arthur Saltzman regarding purchase of James Penney's Oneida Square with notes by Penney)
  - Sm-St, General, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 45)
    (Hughie Lee-Smith; Vernon Smith; Queena Stovall)
  - T, General, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 46)
    (Temple University; Toledo Museum of Art)
  - U, General, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 47)
    (University of Miami Lowe Gallery)
  - University of Nebraska, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 48)
    (selection of Kenneth Evett to create the first set of murals for Nebraska's capitol building)
  - V, General, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 49)
  - W, General, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 50)
  - Wadsworth Atheneum, 1954 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Walker Art Center, 1954 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Whitney Museum of American Art, 1954 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Wilson, Margretta, and Ralph L. Wilson, 1954 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    (arrangements for exhibitions and purchases for Lehigh University)
  - X-Y-Z, General, 1954 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - A, General, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    (Barnett Aden Gallery; Alicia Atkinson)
  - American Academy of Arts and Letters, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - American Federation of Arts, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Ba-Bl, General, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    (John Bernhardt)
  - Bo-Bu, General, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    (Manuel Bromberg)
  - Baltimore Museum of Art, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Brooklyn Museum, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Ca-Coe, General, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    (Yuen Yuey Chinn; Edward Christiana)
  - Col-Cr, General, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Carnegie Institute, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Columbus Gallery of Fine Arts, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Da-Def, General, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Deg-Dy, General, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    (card from Guy Pène and Yvonne Du Bois)
  - "D" Contemporary Paintings, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Dartmouth College, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - De Gregorio, Vincent J., 1955 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Des Moines Art Center, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - E, General, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Fa, General, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Fe-Fu, General, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 25)
    (David Finn of Ruder & Finn Associates regarding a traveling exhibition, Business Meets the Arts)
  - G, General, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 26)
    (Mrs. Walter F. Gips, Jr., regarding a commission for a mobile by George Rickey; Michael Gish)
  - Glover Associates, Inc., 1955 (Box 39, Folder 27)
    (Ruth Martin)
  - Wm. E. Goodridge & Son, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - Grugan, Andrew J., 1955 (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - H, General, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 30)
    (Whitney Ford Hoyt)
  - J. L. Hudson Company, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 31)
  - I, General, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 32)
  - J, General, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 33)
  - K, General, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 34)
    (Kansas State College; Irving Katzenstein)
  - L, General, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 35)
    (Richard Lahey; Lehigh University)
  - Ma, General, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 36)
  - Mc-Mu, General, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 37)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 38)
  - Mount Holyoke College, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 39)
  - Munson-Williams-Proctor Institute, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 40)
  - Museum of Modern Art, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 41)
  - N, General (Woldemar Neufeld), 1955 (Box 39, Folder 42)
  - William Rockhill Nelson Gallery of Art, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 43)
  - O, General, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 44)
  - Pa-Ph, General (Walter Pach), 1955 (Box 39, Folder 45)
  - Pi-Pr, General (Eugenie Prendergast), 1955 (Box 39, Folder 46)
  - Parrish Art Museum, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 47)
  - Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 48)
  - Pennsylvania State University, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 49)
  - Philadelphia Art Alliance, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 50)
  - Q, General, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 51)
  - R, General, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 52)
  - Renaissance Society at the University of Chicago, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 53)
  - Sa-Sc, General, 1955 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Se-So, General, 1955 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    (David Seyler; Hughie Lee-Smith; Vernon Smith; Smithsonian Institution National Collection of Fine Arts)
  - Sp-Sw, General, 1955 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - T, General, 1955 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - U, General, 1955 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    (Union College; University of Minnesota)
  - University of Nebraska, 1955 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - V, General, 1955 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Wa-We, General (Union College; University of Minnesota), 1955 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Wh-Wy, General, 1955 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    (Whitney Museum of American Art; Ralph L. Wilson; Worcester Art Museum)
  - Wadsworth Atheneum, 1955 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Walker Art Center, 1955 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - X-Y-Z, General, 1955 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - A, General, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - American Academy of Arts and Letters, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    (loans for a Gifford Beal exhibition with dates of paintings and insurance values)
  - American Federation of Arts, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    (Sport in Art exhibition)
  - Ba-Bo, General, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    (Birmingham Museum of Art with a letter to Joe Lasker referring to Lasker's protest against the museum in response to "the entire course of events from the Supreme Court decision")
  - Br-Bu, General, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Beal, Rebecca J., 1956 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    (loan and purchase of William Kienbusch pictures)
  - Brooklyn Museum, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    (purchase of Nude with Apples by William J. Glackens)
  - Ca-Cl, General, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    (Yuen Yuey Chinn; Edward Christiana; Albert Christ-Janer)
  - Co-Cu, General, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Carnegie Institute, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 22)
    (purchase of La Villette by William J. Glackens)
  - Carlee, Randolph D. L., 1956 (Box 40, Folder 23)
    (regarding purchase of 2 John Sloan paintings, Red Paint Mill and Off the Nambe Road)
  - Corcoran Gallery of Art, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 24)
    (Institute of Contemporary Arts events at the gallery)
  - Currier Gallery of Art, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 25)
    (Painters by the Sea exhibition)
  - D, General, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 26)
    (Archives of American Art at the Detroit Institute of Arts concerning donation of art auction catalogs and possible donation of a Maurice Prendergast sketchbook)
  - Dayton Art Institute, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - Denver Art Museum, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 28)
    (the museum's Children's Museum regarding Tom Hardy sculpture)
  - E, General, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 29)
    (Allan D. Emil concerning purchase of the Maurice Prendergast painting Summer and Head by Gaston Lachaise; Frank Eyerly)
  - F, General, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - G, General, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 31)
    (Robert Garelick of Garelick's Gallery regarding a John Sloan exhibition and the purchase of 45 etchings)
  - Wm. E. Goodridge & Son, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 32)
    (90 John Sloan etchings on consignment to Kraushaar Galleries from Wayte Raymond that were lost in the move to Madison Avenue in 1955; catalog for a William Kienbusch exhibition with insurance values)
  - H, General, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - Hatfield, Dalzell, and Ruth Hatfield, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - I, General, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 35)
    (Henry Hope of Indiana University Fine Arts Department with his suggested copy for an introduction to a Robert Laurent exhibition catalog)
  - J, General, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 36)
  - K, General, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 37)
  - L, General, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 38)
  - Lehigh University, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 39)
  - Ma, General, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 40)
    (Elsie Manville; George May)
  - Mc-Mi, General, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 41)
    (Metropolitan Museum of Art)
  - Mo-Mu, General, 1956 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    (Mount Holyoke College; Museum of Art of Ogonquit; Museum of Modern Art)
  - Munson-Williams-Proctor Institute, 1956 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Na-Nev, General, 1956 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - New-No, General, 1956 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - O, General, 1956 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Pa-Pe, General, 1956 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Ph-Pu, General, 1956 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Philadelphia Museum of Art, 1956 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    (John Sloan exhibition and purchase of a John Sloan collection by the museum including a price list)
  - Ra-Re, General, 1956 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    (Sidney Raynes; illustrated postcard from Grant T. Reynard)
  - Rh-Ru, General, 1956 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    (Edward G. Robinson regarding a Maurice Prendergast painting)
  - Sa-Se, General, 1956 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Sh-Sy, General, 1956 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Santa Barbara Museum of Art, 1956 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    (Carl Morris exhibition with a letter from Morris thanking the museum and expressing pleasure at the sale of River Night)
  - Schramm, James, 1956 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - T, General, 1956 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - U, General, 1956 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    (University of Colorado; University of Michigan; Mary Washington College at the University of Virgini a)
  - University of Maine, 1956 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    (University of Colorado; University of Michigan; Mary Washington College at the University of Virginia)
  - University of Nebraska, 1956 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - V, General, 1956 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - W, General, 1956 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Wadsworth Atheneum, 1956 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Whitney Museum of American Art, 1956 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Wilson, Ralph L., 1956 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - X-Y-Z, General, 1956 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Ad-Ap, General, 1957 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Ar-At, General, 1957 (Box 41, Folder 26)
    (Ned Archer; Atlanta Art Association)
  - American Federation of Arts, 1957 (Box 41, Folder 27)
    (exhibitions including catalogs for, and information regarding, Fourteen Painter-Printmakers held at Kraushaar Galleries, May-June 1957)
  - Ba-Bo, General, 1957 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Br-Bu, General, 1957 (Box 41, Folder 29)
    (Ainslie Burke concerning a Fulbright-funded year in Italy)
  - Beal, James, and Rebecca Beal, 1957 (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - Bernstein, Irwin L., 1957 (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - Ca-Cl, General, 1957 (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - Co-Cu, General, 1957 (Box 41, Folder 33)
    (Columbia Museum of Art; Columbus Gallery of Fine Arts)
  - Carlee, Randolph D. L., 1957 (Box 41, Folder 34)
  - Cushman Gallery, Inc., 1957 (Box 41, Folder 35)
    (Edward Christiana regarding exhibition of his work)
  - Da-Dc, General, 1957 (Box 41, Folder 36)
    (Dartmouth College; Dayton Art Institute)
  - De-Du, General, 1957 (Box 41, Folder 37)
    (Denver Art Museum; Detroit Institute of Arts concerning the Archives of American Art; Yvonne Du Bois)
  - Des Moines Art Center, 1957 (Box 41, Folder 38)
  - E, General, 1957 (Box 41, Folder 39)
  - F, General, 1957 (Box 41, Folder 40)
  - G, General, 1957 (Box 41, Folder 41)
  - Wm. E. Goodridge, Inc., 1957 (Box 41, Folder 42)
    (catalogs of John Heliker and John Koch exhibitions with insurance notes)
  - H, General, 1957 (Box 41, Folder 43)
    (Charles Hagedorn regarding a sculpture commission by Tom Hardy with photographs of the sculpture's location; Alan Chidsey regarding Marsden Hartley's estate)
  - I, General, 1957 (Box 41, Folder 44)
  - J, General, 1957 (Box 41, Folder 45)
    (Junior League Art Gallery, Inc., in Louisville)
  - Ka-Ke, General, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Ki-Ku, General, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    (David Kimball)
  - La-Le, General, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Li-Ly, General, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    (Library of Congress regarding prints purchased)
  - Lehigh University, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    (illustrated letter from Francis J. Quirk; copies of letters to Ralph Wilson regarding the collection at Lehigh University)
  - Ma-Mc, General, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    (Edward Marcus; George May)
  - Me-My, General, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    (Museum of Art of Ogonquit regarding plans for a Tom Hardy exhibition)
  - Montreal Museum of Fine Arts, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    (loan of The Beach, San Malo for an exhibition of art by William J. Glackens and his friends at Kraushaar Galleries in 1957)
  - Munson-Williams-Proctor Institute, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Museum of Modern Art, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - N, General, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - O, General, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - P, General, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Philadelphia Art Alliance, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Q, General, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Ra, General, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    (Sidney Raynes)
  - Re-Ry, General, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    (3 illustrated postcards from Grant T. Reynard; Sally Robinson)
  - Sa-Se, General, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Sh-Sy, General, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Slater Memorial Museum, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - T, General, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - U, General, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - V, General, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Wa, General, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - We-Wo, General, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Wadsworth Atheneum, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Whitney Museum of American Art, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - X-Y-Z, General, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 28)
    (estate of Mahonri Mackintosh Young, who died in November 1957)
  - Ad-Am, General, 1958 (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Ap-At, General, 1958 (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - American Federation of Arts, 1958 (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Ba-Bi, General, 1958 (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - Bo-Bu, General, 1958 (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - Ca-Ci, General, 1958 (Box 42, Folder 34)
    (Yuen Yuey Chinn in Paris; Edward Christiana)
  - Cl-Col, General, 1958 (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - Con-Cu, General, 1958 (Box 42, Folder 36)
  - Carlee, Randolph D. L., 1958 (Box 42, Folder 37)
    (concerning purchase of Seine at Paris by William J. Glackens)
  - Carr, Mr. and Mrs. F. William, 1958 (Box 42, Folder 38)
  - Cincinnati Art Museum, 1958 (Box 42, Folder 39)
    (museum's Contemporary Arts Center)
  - D, General, 1958 (Box 42, Folder 40)
    (Denver Art Museum; Ralph Dubin)
  - Des Moines Art Center, 1958 (Box 42, Folder 41)
    (Frederick Dwight Kirsch concerning exhibitions at the center, purchase of Maurice Prendergast's Girl in Blue Dress, and personal matters)
  - E, General, 1958 (Box 42, Folder 42)
  - F, General, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    (Perle Fine)
  - G, General, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Wm. E. Goodridge, Inc., 1958 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Ha, General, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - He-Hy, General, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - I, General, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    (Iowa State Teachers College)
  - J, General, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    (Dorothy C. Jack enclosing a photograph of a landscape by Childe Hassam)
  - K, General, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    (Antoinette Kraushaar during her visit to the Walker Art Center)
  - Kimball, David C., 1958 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - La-Les, General, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    (Lehigh University)
  - Lev-Lu, General, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    (Robert Light regarding John Sloan etchings with a marked-up copy of Catalogue of the Complete Collection of Etchings by John Sloan dated February 1937; Don Lord)
  - London, Robert, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Ma-Me, General, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    (John, Jr., and Norma Marin; Marjorie Maxon; George May; Elizabeth McFadden)
  - Mi-My, General, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Museum of Fine Arts, Boston, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    (purchase of 3 works by Maurice Prendergast; letter enclosing notes on all Prendergast paintings handled by Kraushaar Galleries)
  - Museum of Modern Art, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - N, General, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    (Margaret Lawson Nison concerning sales of artwork by Ernest Lawson)
  - O, General, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Pa-Pe, General, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 19)
    (Walter Pach; George Perutz)
  - Ph-Pr, General, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Q, General, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Ra-Rh, General, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 22)
    (Charles Raubicheck; illustrated postcard from Grant T. Reynard; Hedley Rhys concerning his thesis on Maurice Prendergast)
  - Ri-Ru, General, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 23)
    (Grace Root concerning prices and insurance values on her art collection and enclosing a photo postcard of her house; Iver Rose; Irwing Rosenhouse enclosing prices of his prints)
  - Sa-Se, General, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Sh-Sp, General, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 25)
    (Jack Steiger; Harris Steinberg)
  - St, General, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Schermerhorn Gallery, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Smithsonian Institution, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 28)
    (loans for 2 exhibitions)
  - Syracuse Museum of Fine Arts, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - T, General, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 30)
    (Evelyn Taylor; Helen Train)
  - U, General, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - University of Nebraska, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - University of Notre Dame, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - V, General, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 34)
  - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 35)
  - Wa-Wel, General, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 36)
  - Wes-Wy, General, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 37)
    (Esther Williams concerning memories of William J. Glackens; Ralph L. Wilson)
  - Wadsworth Atheneum, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 38)
  - Walker Art Center, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 39)
    (exhibition attended by Antoinette Kraushaar)
  - X-Y-Z, General, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 40)
  - Aa-Al, General, 1959 (Box 43, Folder 41)
  - Am-At, General, 1959 (Box 43, Folder 42)
    (Dorothy Andrews)
  - Ba-Be, General, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    (list of paintings by Cecil Bell on consignment at Kraushaar Galleries)
  - Bi-Bu, General, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    (Bowdoin College Museum of Fine Arts; Brick Store Museum concerning a Peggy Bacon exhibition)
  - Baltimore Museum of Art, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    (Vaughn Flannery memorial exhibition with a list of all Flannery paintings handled by Kraushaar Galleries)
  - Ca-Ch, General, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    (Mary Chenoweth; Yuen Yuey Chinn; Edward Christiana)
  - Ci-Col, General, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    (Coleman Art Gallery; Columbus Gallery of Fine Arts)
  - Com-Cu, General, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Cincinnati Art Museum, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Columbia Museum of Art, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - D, General, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    (Randall Davey; Richard Davis; Worden Day; Werner Drewes)
  - Des Moines Art Center, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    (purchase of Tugs by John Sloan)
  - E, General, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Epstein, Ellen, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - F, General, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - G, General, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Wm. E. Goodridge, Inc., 1959 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    (catalog for a Henry Mitchell exhibition)
  - Grant, Earle, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Ha-Hei, General, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Hel-Hy, General, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Dalzell Hatfield Galleries, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Heinzelman, Carl D., 1959 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - I, General, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - J, General, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - K, General, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 23)
    (Kansas State University; Glen Krause)
  - La-Les, General, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Lev-Lu, General, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 25)
    (Leslie Levy enclosing a photograph of John Sloan's painting Gloucester Bay; Charles Locke)
  - Ma-Me, General, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - Mi-Mu, General, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 27)
    (Adelaide Moise; William Moise)
  - Museum of Modern Art, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - N, General, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - O, General, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - Pa-Pe, General, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 31)
  - Ph-Pr, General, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - Prendergast, Eugenie, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 33)
    (regarding arrangements for handling the work of Charles and Maurice Prendergast including lists of works on consignment from 1956 to 1959
  - Q, General, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 34)
  - R, General, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 35)
    (Sally Robinson)
  - Sa-Sc, General, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 36)
    (Schermerhorn Gallery)
  - Se-So, General, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 37)
    (Ronald Searle)
  - Sp-Sy, General, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 38)
  - Santa Barbara Museum of Art, 1959 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Semans, Mary T., 1959 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - T, General, 1959 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - U, General, 1959 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - V, General, 1959 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Wa-Wh, General, 1959 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Wi-Wy, General, 1959 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Wadsworth Atheneum, 1959 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Wilmington Society of the Fine Arts, 1959 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - X-Y-Z, General, 1959 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Ab-Al, General, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Am-Au, General, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Allentown Art Museum, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Ba-Bl, General, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    (Maud Beal; Rosalie Berkowitz; John Bernhardt)
  - Bo-Bu, General, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Baker, Keith H., 1960 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Brooklyn Museum, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Ca-Cl, General, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Co-Cu, General, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Carnegie Institute, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Columbus Gallery of Fine Arts, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - D, General, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 22)
    (1957 Archives of American Art brochure from Detroit Institute of Arts)
  - Dallas Museum for Contemporary Arts, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 23)
    (exhibition of drawings by Ulfert Wilke)
  - Dartmouth College, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 24)
    (William J. Glackens retrospective exhibition)
  - Dayton Art Institute, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - E, General, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - Fa-Fi, General, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Fl-Fu, General, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 28)
    (Ford Foundation concerning retrospective exhibitions of Carl Morris and Karl Schrag arranged in conjunction with American Federation of Arts)
  - Fillin, Walter, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 29)
    (estimates for value of various pictures)
  - Fleischman, Lawrence, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 30)
  - Ga-Go, General, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 31)
  - Gr-Gu, General, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 32)
  - Wm. E. Goodridge, Inc., 1960 (Box 45, Folder 33)
  - Ha-He, General, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 34)
  - Hi-Hu, General, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 35)
  - I, General, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 36)
  - J, General, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 37)
    (Julius Jacobson)
  - Ka-Kh, General, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 38)
  - Ki-Ku, General, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 39)
    (John Koch; Glen Krause; Antoinette Kraushaar to her employees from her vacation in East Hampton with business and personal news)
  - L, General, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 40)
  - Lehigh University, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 41)
  - Lofstrum, James E., 1960 (Box 45, Folder 42)
  - Ma, General, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 43)
  - Mc-Me, General, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 44)
  - Mi-Mu, General, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 45)
  - Museum of Fine Arts, Boston, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 46)